# CHRISTINA XAMIN

# CONTACT

416 523 3132 cxamin@gmail.com christinaxamin.com

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Surrey Place**

Toronto, ON August 2018-Present

#### Rapid7

Toronto, ON May 2017-September 2017

## **Oakville Public Library**

Oakville, ON May 2016-August 2016

## **EDUCATION**

# Sheridan College

September 2014-April 2018

#### **Sheridan College**

January 2012-May 2014

## **ABOUT**

Ambitious designer with 3+ years experience in a professional environment and a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Additional 4 years of academic design experience at Sheridan College. Background in visual and creative arts. Excellent communication skills.

# **UX/UI** Designer

- Interviewed stakeholders (including interal staff, partners and end users) and translated requirements into research needs, prototypes and testing
- Lead user testing sessions, analyzed findings and provided design updates and recommendations to further projects
- Assisted with development and implementation of system modernization including Dynamics365 CRM
- Designed interfaces to enhance user experiences for both new and existing mobile and web applications

#### Interactive and Technical Media Writer Intern

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

#### **Graphic Design Assistant**

- Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy

#### **Bachelor of Interaction Design**

Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma